[Music]
this days having a medical insurance are
Necessities rather than
luxuries and that is why investing in
critical illness insurance is crucial
because it could protect us from
Financial assertion and insuring our
stability during challenging
times so we choose a credential company
as our insuring policy for this
assignment so let me introduce to you
what is
credential you can get more info about
them on their website
www.prudential.com
credential Assurance Malaysia Bight or
BB is a leading and Innovative insurance
company in Malaysia they provide simple
and accessible financial and Health
Solution to every
generation and as we go to the their
website and we can see there were a lot
of product policy that prenal offer and
one of them was critical illness
Insurance let me explain briefly about
it as we know critical illness can
burden both our well-being and financial
stability that's why it is important to
protect us and our loved one and here
some benefits of critical inner span
first one is
comprehensive coverage for wide range of
critical
illnesses second one is early to lead
stage critical illness coverage the
third one is lome payout to you or your
family and the last one is support for
mental and physical wellbe
Miss I believe your mother also had
cancer
right flashback
this is unfair I don't know what to do
we have no insurance for this it's okay
we figure it out I have someing you can
L I won't lose you okay we we can't use
that she still needs to grow up she
needs the money for her education it's
okay we have life insurance for her but
we have feel to consider critical
illness insurance but don't worry you
must how you have but how about those
trips to Hawaii that you plann is the to
that purpose there's no Hawai and you're
not
[Music]
helpy and a flashback pleas I'm sorry is
it again it's okay me uh as I was saying
your mother had breast cancer if I'm not
mistaken it was stated in your profile
hisory
yes
it's first cancer is genetic disase it
will be best if you take into
consideration And subscribe to our
critical illness insurance policy as
well the critical illness policy
credential has to offer cover the
financial treatment for early to late
stage of critical illnesses including
cancer kidney failure sto Hur attacks
coronary bypass and 186 more disase we
also provide a L some payout of total of
400% of your original coverage 100% each
four different unes so the L some
payment will be made to you or any of
your family members should you face any
critical
un however the amount of H 100% Can
differ according to the sity of the
illness this mean if you face four types
of critical illness we will finish all
four of the eares according to the stage
of the ear we will also provide
comprehensive support for both mental
and physical wellbe this insurance can
consider the numerous Financial aspects
impact such as loss of income daily
living expenses and most importantly our
curreny holder M to being however just
to inform you the plan will exclude its
coverage if the insurance company find
that the the policy of has pre-existing
medical condition or any of the injuries
or illnesses that occur itself
in I see but as of right now I can to
make a decision to sub a new policy yet
can we talk about this L sure no
worries I think I should call
salum hi pu oh Dad how are you I'm doing
fine how are you I'm do great ear today
I met the agent and she about the
subscribing to the new policy oh what
policy is she offering this
time something aboutness and children M
to she said something about breast
cancer being a genetic disas as well oh
I see well she does know a l and she is
the fist agent and perhaps she is wrong
but I don't know that I don't think I
want to come me toate
policy you know dear when your mom had
to go to treatments back then it wasn't
that we had didn't have the money we did
but we had to sacrifice a lot of things
in order to get her the
treatments I know I will well I think
you should consider it if what the issue
agent say is true about breast cancer
being a genetic disease can help a lot
in the
future okay d
i all right I'll talk to you ler byebye
[Music]
okay
okay hello Miss
I decided to subcribe to the insurance
policy that you offered the other day
and I've went to research and realize it
can definitely help me in the future
that's great I get the paperwork done
for you and when it's ready I contact
you as soon as
possible
okay several days
later okay is the is I explain a little
bit more about potential critical
illness insurance
plan so this is the plan there are
over9 critical illnesses that this plan
covers so it's not necessarily used for
breast cancer if you face her attacks
kind of failures so this plan will also
help cover your medical B and living
expenses it can also help with
Transportation expenses including
Journeys to treatment centers with CHS
and even installing Li in your home
however the plan is not trable by the
policy holders for injuries attain from
accidents unless the accidents inflict
permanent disabilities if you agree to
the plan you can give your signature and
conent here
okay thank
[Music]
you this why we need to penetrate the
market as soon as
possible thank you everyone
hello doctor Hi how are you feeling um
I'm not feeling good and I keep feeling
something in my Ed area and there's a
wetness in my chest
area I see do you mind if I check on it
H that's quite
unsettling I believe you must go to the
radiologist Department I can check with
do that all
right so let me get this on in
[Music]
so there's definitely cancer cells
building up in your breast area but it's
in the early stages if you do treatments
now you can have a chance of removing
cancer I see
let me inform my family and we can
arrange the treatment
[Music]
I
you have to go through
this that's
you don't worry plus I have the
insurance and the treatment will go
smoothly will not be by P and will take
all of it okay I'll Ste do for as long
as me and take care of you okay thank
you
congratulations miss you are
f are you sure doctor yes thank you
doctor okay so the insurance company
have called and already seed the
hospital view earlier so I have PL the
caim and you can take your rest at home
for the next 30 to 45 days here and uh
make sure to take your meditation okay
having that insurance was definitely a
smart chance it definitely was thank God
that t me into it well I'm just grateful
that both of my
[Music]
go
[Applause]
[Music]
see is
behind the
scen
yeah I have we can use I won't you
you want to
goai it's
so hey
d i this is me